mris.com 2009-10-27

# Privacy Statement for MRIS, Inc.

## WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

### Effective: 9/1/08

At Metropolitan Regional Information Systems, Inc. (MRIS), we are fully committed to the protection and security of any information that you provide to us as users of our Website. We want you to know that we truly respect and will protect your privacy, so you can enjoy using our services which allow us to better serve your needs.

Our Privacy Policy discloses our approach to privacy and how your personal information is collected and used. Your use of our Website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to the practices it describes.

## What Information We Collect

Generally speaking, our Website is informational. We do not collect any personally identifiable information unless you voluntarily provide it, such as when you provide us account information, submit a complaint or fine appeal form, submit an application to become an MRIS Subscriber, register for or post an entry to our RETS Forum, or send a message to us through our Feedback Form.

As is the case when you visit most Websites, to administer our site, your visit triggers the automatic logging of certain anonymous information about your computer system such as the type of browser you use, the server name and your "IP" (Internet Protocol) address. When your Web browser or email application requests a Web page or email from another computer using the Internet, it automatically gives that computer the "address" where it should send the information. This is called your computer's "IP address". This address does not contain any personally identifiable information.

## How We Protect Your Information

We also want you, our visitors, to know that we take the security of your information very seriously and that we take appropriate measures to protect the files in our data system. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your nonpublic personal information.

You need to know, however, that due to the open communication nature of the Internet we cannot guarantee that communication between you and us, and between us and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties nor can we be responsible for information stolen from our servers or computer systems by information harvesting software which may have the ability to scrape data.

## How We Use Your Information

When we ask you for information, we tell you, or it will be clear, why we need any personally identifying information from you either to fulfill a request from you or to provide information or services to you, such as when you submit an application to become an MRIS Subscriber, register for or post an entry to our RETS Forum, or send a message to us through our Feedback Form.

## We Do Not Sell or Rent Your Personal Information

Aside from our own use of your personal information, we do not share any personal information we may have about you with unaffiliated third parties.

We may, however, have to disclose, transfer, sell or assign your information obtained through this Website, or otherwise in our possession, to a third party as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of MRIS. We may also have to make information obtained through this Website, or otherwise in our possession, available to law enforcement personnel and agencies when requested to do so or as required by law.

## We Want To Provide Only Information You Want or Need

The information we send to you includes product updates, compliance notices, billing notices, and service guides. If you do not wish to receive information from us, you should check the particular communication or the corresponding sections of our Website for opt-out instructions.

## Cookie Technology

Cookie technology is employed on our Website. Cookies help us keep track of the pages that you visit while on our Website. In case you did not know, "cookies" are small text files sent by Web servers to be stored on the computers of Website users. These files often contain personalization settings or unique identifiers to keep track of your information and to help us understand the movements of users within and between Websites.

## You Can Change Your Information

You can update or correct your contact information by logging on to your account at MRIS.com

## Privacy Statement Changes

We reserve the right to change or amend our Privacy Policy to address new issues of privacy and information security and to reflect changes to our Website or business practices. Any new changes and/or amendments will be posted on this page. Each version of this policy may be identified by its effective date which is located at the top of the page.

## Questions About Our Privacy And Information Security Practices

Your visit to this site is subject to both this notice and our Terms of Use.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or procedures, please feel free to contact us as follows: 

or 
  * Metropolitan Regional Information Systems, Inc.  
  9707 Key West Ave., Suite 200  
  Rockville, MD 20850-3915

We will promptly address your inquiry
